Guide to the Conference at Yale University on the Works of B. F. Skinner
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Conference at Yale University on the works of B. F. Skinner
1972-1972
RU 836
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.5
The materials consist of eleven audiotapes of lectures and discussions on the works of psychologist B. F. Skinner sponsored by the Chubb Fellowship Program, Yale University.
Timothy Dwight College (Yale University)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 13-G-3 (YRG 13-G-3), Records of the Fellows of Timothy Dwight College.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by topic.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of eleven audiotapes of lectures and discussions on the works of psychologist B. F. Skinner sponsored by the Chubb Fellowship Program, Yale University.
Behaviorism (Psychology); Congresses and conventions; Forums (Discussion and debate); Lectures and lecturing; Meetings; Audiotapes; Skinner, B. F. (Burrhus Frederic), 1904-1990; Timothy Dwight College (Yale University)
- Records of the conference at Yale University on the works of B. F. Skinner [audiorecordings], 1972; Accession 19ND-A-231
  Scope and Contents
  7" polyester sound reel tapes recorded at 7½"/sec, full track.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
  - Opening address by B.F. Skinner, Yale Art Gallery, 10 AM?. [part 1], 1972 April 18; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 1)
  - Opening address by B.F. Skinner, Yale Art Gallery, 10 AM?. [part 2], 1972 April 18; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 2)
  - Panel discussion #1, "The Psychological Aspects," Yale Law School Auditorium, 3:30 PM. Speakers: B.F. Skinner, Theodore Lidz, Willard Gaylin, and William Kessen. [part 1], 1972 April 18; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 3)
  - Panel discussion #1, "The Psychological Aspects," Yale Law School Auditorium, 3:30 PM. Speakers: B.F. Skinner, Theodore Lidz, Willard Gaylin, and William Kessen. [part 2], 1972 April 18; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 4)
  - Panel discussion #2, "Problems of Planning," Yale Law School Auditorium, 8:30 PM. Speakers: Stephen Spender, (Robert Alan?) Dahl, Zbignew Brzezinski, and Alain Enthoven. [part 1], 1972 April 18; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 5)
  - Panel discussion #2, "Problems of Planning," Yale Law School Auditorium, 8:30 PM. Speakers: Stephen Spender, (Robert Alan?) Dahl, Zbignew Brzezinski, and Alain Enthoven. [part 1], 1972 April 18; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 6)
  - Panel discussion #3, Yale Law School Auditorium, 3 PM. Speakers: B.F. Skinner, Rollo May, Paul Ricoeur, Brand Blanshard, and Jaroslav Pelikan. [part 1], 1972 April 19; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 7)
  - Panel discussion #3, Yale Law School Auditorium, 3 PM. Speakers: B.F. Skinner, Rollo May, Paul Ricoeur, Brand Blanshard, and Jaroslav Pelikan. [part 2], 1972 April 19; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 8)
  - Panel discussion #4, general critique and summation, Yale Law School Auditorium, 8:30 PM. Speakers: Gay, Brogan, Clark, et al. [part 1], 1972 April 19; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 9)
  - Panel discussion #4, general critique and summation, Yale Law School Auditorium, 8:30 PM. Speakers: Gay, Brogan, Clark, et al. [part 2], 1972 April 19; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 10)
  - Panel discussion #4, general critique and summation, Yale Law School Auditorium, 8:30 PM. Speakers: Gay, Brogan, Clark, et al. [part 3], 1972 April 19; audiotape (reel-to-reel) (Box 11)